Guide to the Howard Seifert Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- General Files, Part 1
  - Senior Colloquim A48 Extraterrestrial Life - Class Schedules, Grades, Misc. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - ET Life: Class Schedules, Correspondence, (1967-68) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - ET Life: Schedules and Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - ET Life: Borshader Seminar, (April 9, 1970) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - ET Life: Lecture Notes (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - ET Life: Student Reports (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - ET Life: Reference and Source Materials (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - ET Life: Reference and Source Materials (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - ET Life: AIAA Mount Diablo Section (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - ET Life: Reference and Source Materials: Foothill Junior College District Short Courses (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - ET Life: Reference and Source Materials; Extraterrestrial Life NASA SP-7015 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - ET Life: Notes -, August 1967 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - ET Life: Notes (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - ET Life: Notes (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - ET Life: NASA Technical Report Life Detection by Visual Imaging (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - ET Life: NASA Technical Report Sample Acquisition for Life Detection Experiments (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - AA 283: Reference Materials: AIAA Reprints - 66-674; 66-660; 67-128; 66-87; 66-85; 68-470 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - AA 283: Program, Class Schedules; Records, 1968-69 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Speaker Lecture Notes: System Development Planning by James G. Wenzel (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - National Geographic, (April 1960) (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Deep Submergence Systems Project, (November 24, 1964) (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Progress in Aircraft Design Since 1903 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Microfilm Reel - Unknown Subject (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - AA 280: TV Notes, (Winter 1970) (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - AA 280: TV Notes, (Summer 1969) (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Aerodynamic Noise (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Musical Acoustics (Proposals, Data) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Science of Music Lecture Notes, 1969-1970; FS 3 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - FS 3 Problems and Quizzes, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - FS 3 Source Material and References: The Catgut Acoustical Society (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - FS 3 Science of Music Planning and Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - FS 3 Planning and Correspondence Distribution List, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - FS 3 Program Schedules and Class Records, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - FS 3 Science of Music Notes, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - FS 3 Science of Music Notes, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - FS 166 Problems and Quizzes (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - FS 166 Program Schedules and Class Records (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - FS 166 Lecture Notes, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - FS 166 Science of Music Planning and Correspondence, (1971) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - FS 166 Planning and Correspondence Distribution Lists, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - FS 166 Equipment and Lab Data (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - FS 166 Source Material and References, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - FS 166 Source Material and References, 1969-70 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Research (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Research Proposal (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Technical Information Service Report (in German) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - NAtional Science Foundation Potential Opportunity Report 72-2, March 10, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Sponsored Research in the School of Engineering - The Role of Research Coordination (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Potential Research Topics - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - General Research Plans Bernard Spectra, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Research Planning (Rambo 1970 Essay) (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Steam Rocket (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Steam Rocket (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Steam Rocket (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Laser Doppler -, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Analysis of a Propulsion Device Whose Chamber Conditions are Dependent Upon Time - Bruce G. Wrenn (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Liquid Rockets: Rudi Beichel Aerojet General Corporation (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Chemical Diets, November 27, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Bloomer - Space Telescope (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Electrically Augmented Burners - G. Montes, R. Cushing - Northern Natural Gas Co. (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Bloomer (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Holography Kit (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Vortex Flow (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Oceanology 1967 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Particle Cyclotron, April 11, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Bloomerscope (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Bloomer - Space Telescope, May 10, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Small Kundt Tube, April 21, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Oscillation Droplets, OAR, Vol. 6, No. 3 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Operation of Solid Fuel MHD Generators, C. D. Bangerton, A. H. Peterson, E. E. Covert, March 30, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Experimental Thesis: Particle Drag Coefficient, March 31, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Laser Impact: Laser to Assist Shock Studies (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Miscellaneous on Lasers (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Examining the Anomaly of the Singular Point at Launch of the Tapered Exhaust Velocity Rocket, February 2, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Holography and DCO Plot RFP, November 23, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Subliming Jets, September 1966 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Subliming Rocket (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Lateral-Step Rockets, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Wrenn-MHD Dra, (1961-62 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - OAR Progress 1965 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Power Generation, Electric and Advanced Propulsion (Non-Chemical), November 1965 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Future Satellite to Use Skyhook, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - All-Fluid Control, J. A. King, July 1966 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - John Teem, October 20, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Af Raps Research Log, Technology Week, October 10, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Coanda Effect, Scientific American, June 1966 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Ordnance Topic Search (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Pulse-Electric Propulsion (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - RAdiator Problem (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Resume of John A. Dempsey (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Radiance Characteristics of Interacting Flames William S. Cronk and William A. Schmeling, September 1969 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Drag and Propulsion of Large Satellites in the Ionosphere; an Alfven Propulsion Engine in Space (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - NASA Flight Research Center Programs (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - A New Technique for TVC Control: USTTVC, B. W. Silver, May 31, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Tilt Nozzle (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Pintle Nozzles (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - The Dynamics of Liquids in Moving Containers - A Survey, R. M. Cooper, June 1960 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Notes on UTC Technical Management Conference, October 25, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - JPL Space Programs Summary No. 37-39, Vol. 9 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Subliming Solid (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Micrometeoroid Simulation (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Graduate and Undergraduate Theses (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - JPL Research Activities (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - NASA Bibliography No. 229, ARC Jet Axisymmetric Hall Accelerator, June 1965 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - NASA Bibliography 1229, ARC Jet Axisymmetric Hall Accelerator - PArt II (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Axisymmetric HAll Accelerated ARC with Axial Magnetic Fluid:, S. L. Camacho (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - The Subliming Solid Control Rocket, March 2, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Subliming Jet, December 1966 (Box 8A, Folder 84)
  - Letter (Box 8A, Folder 85)
  - Letter from V. R. Gutman, Review of Selected Papers of the AIAA Meeting at Palo Alto, January 29, 1964 (Box 8A, Folder 86)
  - Aerospace Theses Topics List, January 1963 (Box 8A, Folder 87)
  - NASA Technical Reports List, Misc. Notes (Box 8A, Folder 88)
  - AFRPL Planning Brochure, 1965 (Box 8A, Folder 89)
  - Electrical Control of Solid Propellant Burning, P. J. MAyo, L. A. Watermeieeer, F. J. Weinberg, 1965 (Box 8A, Folder 90-91)
  - Stilt-Walking Elaboration (Box 8A, Folder 92)
  - AA Department Published Reports Listing, Miscellaneous Notes (Box 8A, Folder 93)
  - Unlabelled Notes (Box 8A, Folder 94)
  - Shaking a Rocket to Death, Research Review, September 1966 (Box 8A, Folder 95)
  - Technology Week. 6th Annual NASA Issue, November 28, 1966 (Box 8A, Folder 96)
  - E. Fields and Combustion (Box 8A, Folder 97)
  - NSF-ONR Proposal Calls (Box 8A, Folder 98)
  - De Bra - Microthruster - Electrical Energy, August 26, 1970 (Box 8A, Folder 99)
  - Thesis - General Planning; Hall-Airport City, 1969 (Box 8A, Folder 100)
  - Potential Research Topics and Engineering Thesis - General Planning, Cohen 70's Rocket Forecast, No. 2 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - General Planning, Sublimation, April 8, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - General Planning, Miscellaneous Notes (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - General Planning, Lehan, Potential Research, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - General Planning, Steam Rocket Booster, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - General Planning, Dr. Harold Wooster, Reducing (Foods and Metabolism), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - General Planning, Research Opportunities Related to Technical Problems, February 1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Holography and Its Applications (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Park Rocket - Point Lite Source, Christie Electric Corporation (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Park Rocket, March 20, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Chase-BAllistics, Contents of Engineering Thesis, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Hop Toy (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Bloomer, 1968-71 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Bloomer-Lasers, Discraft Corporation, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - David V. Kalbaugh, Park Rocket, June 1968 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Auhll-Pogo: AA 290 Auhll Design Study (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Huddleston (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Huddleston - Kundt's Tube, June 1968 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Huddleston - Acoustic Particle, April 14, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Huddleston - Correspondence and E. S. forces (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Huddleston - Kundts Tube, Babcock Photos (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - On the Circulations Caused by the Vibration of Air in a Tube (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Huddleston - Kundts Tube, Thermistor Explorations in a Kundt Tube (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Andrews - Electrical Properties (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Feasibility of Hybrid Pyrotechnic Signature Generation Techniques (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Lai-UTC Feasibility of Hybrid Pyrotechnic Signature Generation Techniques (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Lai-UTC An Approach to Scaling of Flame Irradiance, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Hybrid Demonstration - Bunn (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Placer - Investigation of Flow Fields Due to Retro-Jets and Their Use for Vehicle Drag Modulation (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Research and Scholarship Table, 1974-75 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Aero #16A-66 Measurement of Particle Velocity in Gas-PArticle 2-Phase Flow by Laser-Doppler Technique (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Aero No. 9-65, Proposal for the Research and Measurement of Particles (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Monthly Reports (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Study Calculations and Reports, Present Status of Particle Velocity Determination Using Opticle Doppler Reader, L. F. Mollenauer (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - SUDAARS Application of Laser-Doppler Technique to Measure Two-Phase Flow, R. N. James, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Study Calc./Reports, Early Study Notes, Colloidal Propulsion (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Study Calc./Reports, Preliminary Survey of Colloidal Propulsion Particle Size and Charge Requirement, R. N. James (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Proposal, The Role of Research Coordination (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Proposal, New Proposal for Research Submitted to Project Squid (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Colloidal Proposal Research, J. P. Kesserling, 1964-1967 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - SUDAARS Publications, Colloid Propulsion Negatives and Photos (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - SUDAARS Publications, The Use of Preformed Solid Particles... Kesserling, Seifert, October 1968 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Development of a Solid-Charged Colloidal Particle Thruster (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Colloidal Preparation - Appendix 1 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Electrical Propulsion with Colloidal Materials (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Reference and Source Materials, Onboard Colloidal Particle for Electrostatic Engines C. T. Norgren (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Decomposition of a Liquid Jet Injected Normal to A Supersonic Air Stream, June 1972 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - TVC File Index (From UTC to March 1984) (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Comptes Rendus TVC, JAnuary 1963 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Opposing Jets, September 1962 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - TVC Reference and Source Material, Study of Secondary Injection of Gases Into Supersonic Flow (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Broadwell-STL-Blast Wave, March 15, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Schgal-Wu, JPL, July 1963 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Proposal, Laser Analysis of Rocket Exhaust with A Condensed Phase, July 8, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Proposal, Measurement of Particle Velocity in Gas-Particle Two-Phase Flow by a Laser-Doppler Technique, July 7, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Security Guide (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Bi-Monthly Reports and Summaries: Laser Doppler, (3 Binders) (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - SUDAARS Publications, Development of Laser-Doppler Particle Sensor... Morse, Tullis, Seifert and Babcock (Box 9A, Folder 58)
  - Optical and IR Properties of AL2O3 at Elevated Temperatures (Box 9A, Folder 59)
  - Reference and Source Material, Temperature Dependence of the m,e Scattering and Absorption Cross Sections for Aluminum Oxide (Box 9A, Folder 60)
  - Reference and Source Material, Experimental Investigation of the Opacity of Small Particles, P. J. MArteney, NASA CR-211, April 1965 (Box 9A, Folder 61)
  - Dan Particles (Box 9A, Folder 62)
  - Reference and Source Materials, Mechanism of Particle Collision in the One-Dimensional Dynamics of Gas-Particle Mixtures, Frank E. Marble, August 1964 (Box 9A, Folder 63)
  - Reference and Source Materials, Gas Velocity Measurement Using Scattering Techniques, Foreman, George, Jenson (Box 9A, Folder 64)
  - Reference and Source Material, Exhaust Particle Size Data (Box 9A, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 9A, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 9A, Folder 67)
  - Laser Doppler: Proposal and Planning, 1971 (Box 9A, Folder 68)
  - Laser Doppler: Proposal and Planning, 1969-70 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Research, Laser Doppler - Contract, 1969-70 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Financial: 1969, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Laser Doppler, Periodic Reports, 28-Sep-70 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Investigation of Particle Size in Two-Phase Exhausts by Means of the Optical Response of a Laser-Doppler Velocimeter, and notes (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Laser Doppler Paper (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Project Squid Note, Report (Loose) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Study Calculations/Reports, AF Propulsion Laboratory Two-Phase Flow Conference, March, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - SUDAARS and Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Investigation of Particle Size in Two-Phase Exhausts by Means of the Optical Response of a Laser-Doppler Velocimeter, November 1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Photos - Glass Beads Under White and Laser Light - Assorted Magnifications (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Squid Final Report (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - An Experimental Investigation of Turbulent Diffusion; notes and memos, July 6, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Particle Flow in Turbomachinery with Application to Laser-Doppler Velocimetry (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Development of a Laser-Doppler Particle Sensor for the Measurement of Velocities in Rocket Exhaust, Seifert, et al (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Investigation of Particle Size in Two-Phase Exhausts by Means of the Optical Response of a Laser-Doppler Celocimeter (loose), Andrews, Seiffert, (2 copies) (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Laser Anemometry (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Frontiers of Laser Development (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Investigation of Particle-Size Determination from the Optical Response of a Laser-Doppler Velocimeter, D. Andrews, H. Seiffert, November 1971; (2 copies) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - The Optical Response of a Laser-Doppler Sensing Instrument in Measurements of High Velocity Particle-Entraining Flows, Tullis, January, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Use of Lasers for Local Measurement of Velocity Components, Species Densities and Temperatures, Penner, Jerskey (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Reference and Source Material (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Laser-Doppler Velocity Measurements of Swirling Flows with Upstream Influence, Orloff and Bossel, July 1973 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Study of Laser Backscatter by Particulates in Stock Emissions, April 23, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Measurement of Particle Drag Coefficients in Flow Regimes Encountered by Particles in a Rocket Nozzle, Crowe, Babcock, Willoughby, Carbon (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Calculation of Scattered Patterns from Asymmetrical Reflectors, Ludwig, February 15, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Project Squid: Semi-annual Progress Report, May 1, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Investigation of Supersonic Phenomena in a Two-Phase Tunnel, Eddington, January 1970 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Dusty Hypersonic Flows, Probstein, Fassio (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Mechanism of Particle Collision in the One-Dimensional Dynamics of Gas-particle Mixtures, Marble, August 1964 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Philco-Ford (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Outline - Final Squid Report (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Pre-IDA (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - LDV-RFP (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Laser-Doppler Instruction Manual Manuscript (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Dana Andrews: Thesis Rough Draft (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Dana Andrews: Thesis (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Dana Andrews: Final Thesis (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Particle Size LDV-Andrews, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Current LDV (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Development of a Laser-Doppler Particle Sensor for the Measurement of Velocities in Rocket Exhausts, Seiffert, et al (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - IDA Trip - December 14-15, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - LDV References (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - L. G. Correspondence-TV Publicity (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Engineering Notes - The Lunar Pogo Stick, Journal of Spacecraft, Vol. 4, No. 7, pp. 941-943, July 1967 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Art Work: Pogo, color and black and white (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Kaplan-Grasshopper Theory, 1967/68 Dissertation Outline (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Small Scale Lunar Surface Personnel Transporter Employing the Hopping Mode, Seifert, et al, September 1, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Supporting Calculations and Studies - earliest notes, May 23, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Meeting, Ronald J. - Proposal Comments, Thermodynamic Analysis of the Process of Letting Gas from the Reaction Chamber into the Piston for a Lunar Pogo Stick Using Anhydrous Hydrazine, December 7, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Pogo Notebook, Meeting (Box 10A, Folder 51)
  - Lunar Grasshopper Proposal Critique, NASA Critique (Box 10A, Folder 52)
  - Kaplan Proposal, 1974 (Box 10A, Folder 53)
  - Kaplan Proposal - Small Scale Lunar Surface Personnel Transporter Employing the Hopping Mode (Box 10A, Folder 54)
  - Formal Pogo Proposals (Box 10A, Folder 55)
  - Kaplan Hopper Proposal, (Envelope) (Box 10A, Folder 56)
  - Semi-Annual Status Report, Small Scale Lunar Surface Personnel Transporter Employing the Hopping Mode, September 1968; (loose) (Box 10A, Folder 57)
  - AIAA Paper: Hopping Transporter for the Lunar Explorer, October 1968 (Box 10A, Folder 58)
  - Pogo Publicity (Box 10A, Folder 59)
  - Renewal Proposal for Research on a Small-Scale Lunar Surface Personnel Transporter Employing the Hopping Mode, March 9, 1970 (Box 10A, Folder 60)
  - Ames Pogo Review, May 21, 1970 (Box 10A, Folder 61)
  - Pogo Pictures (Box 10A, Folder 62)
  - Meetin/Seifert - Closed Cycle Problem (Box 10A, Folder 63)
  - Meetin/Seifert (Box 10A, Folder 64)
  - Meetin Papers, (envelope) (Box 10A, Folder 65)
  - Meetin Papers, (envelope) (Box 10A, Folder 66)
  - Minutes of Pogo Meetings -, 4/3/68 to 12/17/69; (binder) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Pogo Notes, 1968-70; (binder) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Pogo Demonstrator Publicity (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - NASA Grant - Reference and Source Material (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Manned Propulsion Devices and Their Application On Earth and In Space, Seale and Emerson (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Reference/Source Material, Experimental Investigation of Ultahigh Vacuum Adhesion as Related to the Lunar Surface, JAnuary 1 to December 31, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Synoptic Paper and Kaplan Plane-Change (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Kaplan Plane-Change and Proposal (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Pogo Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Meetin Pogo Paper (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Kaplan-Meetin-Pogo Correspondence, Proposal (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Pogo Closed System and Proposal (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Design Specification Grove - Mity-Mite Regulator, October 1967 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Lunar Grasshopper (Pogo) Page Demonstrator... Propulsion Tests (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Pogo Demonstrator - Drawings and Reports, (pictures) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Robotics (spires) Compendex (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Ph.D. Qualifying Examinations beginning May 1970 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Ph.D. Qualifying Examinations (Examination question Types -, January 15, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Notes, Qualifications, Etc., May 1971 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Qualifying Examinations, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Ph.D. Examinations, (confidential), May 1970 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Ph.D. Qualifying Examinations, January 1970 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Ph.D. Qualifying Examinations, (confidential), January 1969 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Ph.D. Qualifying Examinations, January and May 1968 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Ph.D. Qualifying Examination Results - (confidential), January 12 and 13, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Ph.D. Qualifying Examinations, 1966-67 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Ph.D. Qualifying Examinations, Enrollment to 1964 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Ph.D. Qualifying Examinations, Oral Scores, 1962-64 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - General Finances, 1971-74 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Long-term Plans, Stanford Documents (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Administration and Planning, UPL-CIT REIN's, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Long-term Plans - Propulsion, August 22, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Long-term Plans - Space Task Group (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Long-term Plans - Plans, Aero and Astro Department, Space Committee, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Department Brochure, Aero/Astro, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Department Brochures (Engineering Department) Faculty Directory, 1969-70, 1971-72 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Department Brochures - Thermo. Sciences, Engineering Education at Stanford, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Department Brochures History to 1963 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Affiliates, 1975-76 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Affiliates, May 6-7, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Affiliates, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Affiliates, (University), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Afiliates, Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Department Brochures, Affiliates and Alumni Newsletter (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Affiliates, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Affiliates, Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Stanford University Affiliates Notes, May 1973 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Affiliates and Sponsors, 1970-71 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Affiliates Remarks by HSS to First Annual Meeting: SU Affiliates - Kesselring and Tulles, April 11, 1960 (Box 11A, Folder 49)
  - Affiliates Stanford for Engineering (Box 11A, Folder 50)
  - Internal Affairs Committee (Box 11A, Folder 51)
  - Lecturer Appointments The News President: Kenneth S. Pitzer, 1968 (Box 11A, Folder 52)
  - Facilities Major Equipment for Next Decade (Box 11A, Folder 53)
  - Facilities Propulsion Teaching Lab, July 26, 1966 (Box 11A, Folder 54)
  - Curriculum - Stanford University Freshman Seminars, 1967-68 (Box 11A, Folder 55)
  - Curriculum -, 1970-71, 1973 (Box 11A, Folder 56)
  - Aero/Astro Department Administration- Professor Wells Notes on AA 241, 1970 (Box 11A, Folder 57)
  - Curriculum - 280 A, B, C - Outlines, et al (Box 11A, Folder 58)
  - Curriculum - Underwater Propulsion or Hydronautics (Box 11A, Folder 59)
  - Curriculum - Planning: First 280A -, 1960 (Box 11A, Folder 60)